<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Dynamics365 on Blog My Life</title><link>https://www.nashome.cn/tags/dynamics365/</link><description>Recent content in Dynamics365 on Blog My Life</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>zh-CN</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 09:26:29 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.nashome.cn/tags/dynamics365/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>如何将生产环境数据还原到 Dev 环境(Dynamics 365 How to Restore Live Data to Dev)</title><link>https://www.nashome.cn/posts/dynamics-365-how-to-restore-live-data-to-dev/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 09:26:29 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.nashome.cn/posts/dynamics-365-how-to-restore-live-data-to-dev/</guid><description>This blog post is for my notes, you can find more details on Microsoft link. There are some extra steps in the Microsoft link, which I never used. I usually follow only these steps and it works for me. So Instead I need to search on Microsoft link. I wrote this post for my future use. Step 1: You have to restore production database to UAT and then from uat to export it to Asset library Step 2: Download Backpac file in specific location Step 3: Open Command prompt with run as administrator for locally hosted VM and go to following location</description></item><item><title>Dynamics 365 Pre Go Live Checklist</title><link>https://www.nashome.cn/posts/dynamics-365-pre-go-live-checklist/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 17:03:19 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.nashome.cn/posts/dynamics-365-pre-go-live-checklist/</guid><description>Pre Go-live Health Check list: Solution acceptance by users: UAT Is UAT completed successfully? How many users participated in UAT? Did UAT test cases cover entire scope of requirements planned for go-live? How many bugs/issues from UAT are still open? Any of the open bugs/issues a showstopper for go-live? Was UAT done using migrated data? Business signoff: Business has signed off after UAT that the solution meets business needs?</description></item><item><title>Dynamics 365 Selecting the Correct Tier Level on Your Sandboxes</title><link>https://www.nashome.cn/posts/dynamics-365-selecting-the-correct-tier-level-on-your-sandboxes/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 16:46:16 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.nashome.cn/posts/dynamics-365-selecting-the-correct-tier-level-on-your-sandboxes/</guid><description>When purchasing Dynamics 365 F&amp;amp;O, you a get of Microsoft managed (but self-service) environments that is included with the standard offer. (Production, Tier-2 Standard Acceptance Testing and a Tier-1 Develop/Build and test environment.)
Microsoft have described this on the environment planning docs. I will not discuss Tier-1 environments here, as these environments is optimized for development experiences. Do not perform performance testing on a tier-1 environment. Tier-2+ environments is based on the same architecture as a production environment and uses the Azure SQL Database service.</description></item><item><title>Dynamics 365 货运集装箱标签指南</title><link>https://www.nashome.cn/posts/dynamics-365-shipping-container-labeling-guide/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 16:39:38 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.nashome.cn/posts/dynamics-365-shipping-container-labeling-guide/</guid><description>Major retailers have identified incorrect logistic unit (pallet) labeling as a major emerging supply chain issue. A recent sample audit found that approximately 44% of pallet labels are not meeting agreed upon industry requirements. The issues they face include:
No label has been applied Label is in the wrong location Information on the label does not match what is on the pallet Multiple labels with different Serial Shipping Container Codes (SSCC) been applied Pallet label will not scan Stretch-wrap has been applied over the pallet label so it doesn’t scan The following information contains guidelines and general information on how to create and apply good quality logistic (pallet) labels as per the standard requirements of the Retail Industry.</description></item><item><title>Dynamics 365 Supply Structures in Grocery Retail Industry</title><link>https://www.nashome.cn/posts/dynamics-365-supply-structures-in-grocery-retail-industry/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 16:33:31 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.nashome.cn/posts/dynamics-365-supply-structures-in-grocery-retail-industry/</guid><description>Author link: https://en.gravatar.com/hatlevik
Today I will write a bit about the supply chain structure we see in the retail grocery industry, and challengers Dynamics 365 may face, and how to address them. The grocery industry has for many years seen that industry collaboration brings benefits and synergies throughout the value chain. We see industry collaboration that offers a range of services to its owners, customers and partners. In the country where I’m from, the main collaboration initiative is TradeSolution, and is owned by the main grocery chains in Norway.</description></item><item><title>如何将 UAT 的数据在上线时部署到生产环境(How to Deploy UAT Data to Production Server in Dynamics 365)</title><link>https://www.nashome.cn/posts/dynamics-365-how-to-deploy-non-production-data-to-production-server/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 15:03:59 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.nashome.cn/posts/dynamics-365-how-to-deploy-non-production-data-to-production-server/</guid><description>前言 首先这次的操作并不是官方推荐的，但是在绝大多数上线的时候，主数据都是在UAT环境配置和测试，并且绝大多数的应用顾问或者用户都不希望做这种重复劳动，他们太忙了吧～
然而系统并没有提供可以直接部署或者还原的功能，那么我们就创建一个Service Request给微软吧。
Service Request 登录 LCS，打开 Project Details ,创建一个新的Service request
如下图：
新建
如下图：
选择 Sandbox to production
如下图：
接下来需要选择 Sandbox source 、downtime 等等
提交
勾选所有选项后提交吧，提示说这个过程至少需要5个小时的停机时间，但是绝大多数情况1小时左右就能完成了。</description></item><item><title>How to create deployable packages in Dynamics 365</title><link>https://www.nashome.cn/posts/dynamics-365-deployable-packages/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:25:29 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.nashome.cn/posts/dynamics-365-deployable-packages/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Dynamics 365 On-premises Environments</title><link>https://www.nashome.cn/posts/dynamics-365-on-premises/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 14:24:30 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.nashome.cn/posts/dynamics-365-on-premises/</guid><description/></item><item><title>How to deploy instance in Dynamics 365</title><link>https://www.nashome.cn/posts/dynamics-365-instance-deploy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 13:53:26 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.nashome.cn/posts/dynamics-365-instance-deploy/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>