<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ax2012 on Blog My Life</title><link>https://www.nashome.cn/tags/ax2012/</link><description>Recent content in Ax2012 on Blog My Life</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>zh-CN</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 15:11:59 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.nashome.cn/tags/ax2012/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dynamics AX Upgrade to Cu9</title><link>https://www.nashome.cn/dynamics-ax-upgrade-to-cu9/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 15:11:59 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.nashome.cn/dynamics-ax-upgrade-to-cu9/</guid><description>Dynamics AX 2012 R3 CU 9更新：分步 自CU 9发布以来已经有一段时间了，本文简要介绍了如何为已安装的Microsoft Dynamics AX 2012 R3 CU8安装累积更新9。 如果您尝试将MS Dynamics AX 2012 R3 CU 9作为新安装进行安装，请这样做，例如slipstream（ 在新安装（slipstreaming）中包括累积更新和修补程序 ）安装。
安装方式：
在新安装的MS Dynamics AX 2012 R3 CU 9上使用设置向导和补充流程。 使用更新向导将CU9应用到MS Dynamics AX 2012 R3 CU 8的现有安装上。 我们可以从Microsoft Dynamics Lifecycle Services直接安装CU 9，也可以使用Microsoft Dynamics Lifecycle Services和PartnerSource中都提供的Dynamics AX安装程序进行安装。 我们将在这里学习有关使用LCS的Dynamics AX安装程序安装CU 9的信息。
环境准备：
备份业务和模型存储数据库。 备份正在更新的数据库。 确保您是本地计算机上的Admin和Dynamics AX中的系统管理员。 确保您是SQL Server实例上“ SecurityAdmin”服务器角色的成员。 确保您是模型数据库中的“ db_owner”角色。 在安装此更新（或停机）时，请确保系统以单用户模式运行。 下载更新安装程序：
登录到PartnerSource或Microsoft Dynamics生命周期服务 。 下载更新安装程序的最新版本。 在计算机上保存并解压缩更新安装程序以应用更新。 单击更新安装程序后，选择提取文件的路径。 ]</description></item><item><title> Walkthrough: Extending RunBaseBatch Class to Create and Run a Batch</title><link>https://www.nashome.cn/dynamics-ax-run-a-batch/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 09:55:23 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.nashome.cn/dynamics-ax-run-a-batch/</guid><description>Walkthrough: Extending RunBaseBatch Class to Create and Run a Batch Applies To: Microsoft Dynamics AX 2012 R3, Microsoft Dynamics AX 2012 R2, Microsoft Dynamics AX 2012 Feature Pack, Microsoft Dynamics AX 2012
You can design your own batch job by extending the RunBaseBatch class. You can also write code to schedule the batch to run.
By default, after a batch is scheduled, the batch is no longer associated with the client.</description></item><item><title>Dynamics AX Record Level Security</title><link>https://www.nashome.cn/dynamics-ax-record-level-security/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 09:21:37 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.nashome.cn/dynamics-ax-record-level-security/</guid><description>Record Level Security Applies To: Microsoft Dynamics AX 2012 R3, Microsoft Dynamics AX 2012 R2, Microsoft Dynamics AX 2012 Feature Pack, Microsoft Dynamics AX 2012, Microsoft Dynamics AX 2009
Record-level security (RLS) is automatically handled by the kernel when a form or report is opened. However, record-level security is bypassed in the following situations:
Using display and edit methods Using FormListControl, FormTreeControl or TableListControl to show data Using a temporary table as a data source You can enable the Database trace option to view messages that indicate when record-level security is applied to a method call.</description></item></channel></rss>